{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/4234","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4234","name":"Mangonadas Del Barrio","address":"1210-14 Lawndale","zipcode":"48209","owner":"Antonio Hernandez","licenseNumber":"070062","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.12717,42.30178","geojson":{"id":"4234","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.127173226,42.301782064]},"properties":{"name":"Mangonadas Del Barrio","owner":"Antonio Hernandez","address":"1210-14 Lawndale","zipcode":"48209","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"070062","establishmentid":"4234","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622764","name":"Tres Leches 'n Snacks","address":"1210 Lawndale St.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"370","name":"Los Compadres","address":"1132 Lawndale","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3613","name":"Tacos El Toro #1","address":"8191 Chamberlain","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4333","name":"Tacos El Toro #4","address":"8191  Chamberlain St.","zipcode":null},{"establishmentid":"4241","name":"Tacos El Toro #3","address":"8191 Chamberlain","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51623625","name":"LA Palapa Del Parian ","address":"1631 Lawndale ","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4990","name":"Marisqueria El Emperio","address":"1633 Lawndale","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4803","name":"El Parian Commissary","address":"1633 Lawndale","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3383","name":"La Terraza","address":"1633  Lawndale","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4960","name":"El Parian Commissary","address":"1633 Lawndale","zipcode":"48209"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"57389","inspectionDate":"2022-02-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Thermometer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."}]},{"inspectionid":"53893","inspectionDate":"2021-01-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-02-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between supply line and flood rim of","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"SINKS","subLocation":"Spray arm","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-02-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."}]},{"inspectionid":"48748","inspectionDate":"2019-08-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at restroom handsink employee","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Handwashing soap","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"window(s)","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"Windows","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-08-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Ceiling fan","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-08-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"43125","inspectionDate":"2018-07-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"39282","inspectionDate":"2017-07-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-07-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-07-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-601.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be offered for human consumption in a way that does not mislead or misinform the CONSUMER.   \n(B) FOOD or COLOR ADDITIVES, colored overwraps, or lights may not be used to misrepresent the true appearance, color, or quality of a FOOD.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-07-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4234"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}